[
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a software tool used for searching and installing software packages on Debian and Debian-based Linux distributions?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "rpm",
            "answer_b": "apt-rpm",
            "answer_c": "yum",
            "answer_d": "apt-get",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Linux"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_d"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "What command is used to clear up the command prompt window?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "clearit",
            "answer_b": "clrwin",
            "answer_c": "clear",
            "answer_d": "clrscr",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Linux"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    },
    {
        "id": 686,
        "question": "Which command can be used to write onto other currently logged in user\u00e2\u20ac\u2122s console output terminal.",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "notify",
            "answer_b": "alert",
            "answer_c": "write",
            "answer_d": "broadcast",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "BASH"
            }, {
                "name": "Linux"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_c"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "When do we use the GREP command",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "When we want to search for a string",
            "answer_b": "To find a file",
            "answer_c": "To find a directory",
            "answer_d": "To show all directories which have the string in their name",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Linux"
            }, {
                "name": "BASH"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "Which is the best tool to use for logging in remotely?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "rsh",
            "answer_b": "ssh",
            "answer_c": "telnet",
            "answer_d": "login",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Linux"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_b"
    }, {
        "id": 713,
        "question": "Which command can be used to stop the current executing process in the background?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "kill",
            "answer_b": "stop",
            "answer_c": "remove",
            "answer_d": "rm",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "BASH"
            }, {
                "name": "Linux"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 695,
        "question": "Which command can be used to change file access permission bits?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "chmod",
            "answer_b": "chown",
            "answer_c": "umask",
            "answer_d": "chperm",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "BASH"
            }, {
                "name": "Linux"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 681,
        "question": "Who designed the Linux OS?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "Linus Torvalds",
            "answer_b": "Steve Jobs",
            "answer_c": "Steve Wozniak",
            "answer_d": "Steve Linus",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Linux"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "Which of the following is a text editor that can be used in command mode to edit files on a Linux system?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "vi or vim",
            "answer_b": "lsof",
            "answer_c": "open",
            "answer_d": "edit",
            "answer_e": null,
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "Linux"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }, {
        "id": 678,
        "question": "In which directory by default user home directories are created?",
        "answers": {
            "answer_a": "/home",
            "answer_b": "/usr",
            "answer_c": "/tmp",
            "answer_d": "/etc",
            "answer_e": "/user",
            "answer_f": null
        },
        "tags": [
            {
                "name": "BASH"
            }, {
                "name": "Linux"
            }
        ],
        "category": "Linux",
        "difficulty": "Easy",
        "correct_answer": "answer_a"
    }
]
